{
  "quizdata": [
    {
      "questionID": "0607e3cd-5aa2-4fe0-b19f-75132a9d180e",
      "question": "Which is your fav color ?",
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "61c4d699-d5ff-4b02-b645-ea01e0c60582",
          "optionValue": "Blue"
        },
        {
          "id": "80cb0c63-f1a2-40b6-9d12-e57dd6707c65",
          "optionValue": "Black"
        },
        {
          "id": "b12b3a1f-ce86-4d79-ab51-56731854151a",
          "optionValue": "Green"
        },
        {
          "id": "f192ea6b-9040-43ba-831c-9d44e670e472",
          "optionValue": "Grey"
        }
      ],
      "answerkey": "80cb0c63-f1a2-40b6-9d12-e57dd6707c65",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "questionID": "cd07bbd0-18fc-4016-bd1a-064f89aa8b7a",
      "question": "Which is your fav Movie?",
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "2b038201-ddf8-49fa-a0f9-c1afa11f03b2",
          "optionValue": "OM"
        },
        {
          "id": "553dffb1-d18a-4b27-8657-333ad272197d",
          "optionValue": "URI"
        },
        {
          "id": "0eca3a3f-2f23-4b2e-a71c-81fab080372d",
          "optionValue": "ACTION"
        },
        {
          "id": "ac45e4cc-c4d7-4949-b09f-7e521a5ed220",
          "optionValue": "Etc"
        }
      ],
      "answerkey": "553dffb1-d18a-4b27-8657-333ad272197d",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "questionID": "e82d8ecc-1bdd-436c-9a72-e120383989ca",
      "question": "Which is your favorite Nation?",
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "214fc3f0-bfd7-46bd-914e-55881a0f0b44",
          "optionValue": "India"
        },
        {
          "id": "1a06e711-7ae2-49cd-b262-c04b12e55a75",
          "optionValue": "USA"
        },
        {
          "id": "0acce2a6-c233-4055-bdec-70b6cf21adf6",
          "optionValue": "UK"
        },
        {
          "id": "285265f4-0094-4adf-9795-d40d51de8546",
          "optionValue": "Germeny"
        }
      ],
      "answerkey": "214fc3f0-bfd7-46bd-914e-55881a0f0b44",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "questionID": "e7fe49d7-5219-413e-8920-94e638f45f7b",
      "question": "How do you spend your weekend?",
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "8a02d21b-946d-4fb0-97a2-db3d3d4879b3",
          "optionValue": "With Friends"
        },
        {
          "id": "51a99c76-8bac-408c-a015-d0484ab9b6d6",
          "optionValue": "With Life Partner"
        },
        {
          "id": "0dfe1df0-9985-41f4-a6ac-379ee0f845c7",
          "optionValue": "With Family"
        },
        {
          "id": "99a23475-0aa0-4ed1-b032-e5e7b29b8071",
          "optionValue": "With Cousin"
        }
      ],
      "answerkey": "51a99c76-8bac-408c-a015-d0484ab9b6d6",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "questionID": "83c29ddd-eb25-4a6c-bf11-fb23c35b9b4b",
      "question": "Which is your favourite game?",
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "a13228a8-d447-44e9-a6d5-e149b6bf4c7a",
          "optionValue": "Cricket "
        },
        {
          "id": "df6155b5-ecab-423a-8b8c-4ebfdaaa1049",
          "optionValue": "Football"
        },
        {
          "id": "39ab00a1-353b-4275-a418-02d34d13a2aa",
          "optionValue": "Gully Cricket"
        },
        {
          "id": "ba98945e-a6d1-47fa-8553-de9fa1231b57",
          "optionValue": "Basket Ball"
        }
      ],
      "answerkey": "a13228a8-d447-44e9-a6d5-e149b6bf4c7a",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "questionID": "20ff9eb4-c38f-4df5-a9d1-b4fdfc8e5d4b",
      "question": "Which is your favorite indor Game?",
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "692d4f00-20fc-415b-8245-87a178db187a",
          "optionValue": "Mindi"
        },
        {
          "id": "b53ded79-7f07-4c86-86d7-9cfe9e2391d0",
          "optionValue": "Rummy"
        },
        {
          "id": "7d97504f-0abb-4dab-b72b-79ff3623b540",
          "optionValue": "Ludo"
        },
        {
          "id": "5237d285-c6d3-4683-b17e-0ee655556581",
          "optionValue": "Chopat"
        }
      ],
      "answerkey": "692d4f00-20fc-415b-8245-87a178db187a",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "questionID": "9e3bd5df-5524-4312-b2a4-614ea7435e30",
      "question": "Which is your favourite Horror Movie?",
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "0df25198-0cf1-41d7-8f3b-b6c80bb9a6c1",
          "optionValue": "1920 : London"
        },
        {
          "id": "82cf152b-445f-4621-a54c-3ef4d7b2984f",
          "optionValue": "Bhoot"
        },
        {
          "id": "4b265525-62df-42d9-808a-5247f5d14cf2",
          "optionValue": "Enabells"
        },
        {
          "id": "1ec9b6f1-0942-4411-b7ce-1ad498dd2bf6",
          "optionValue": "The Nun"
        }
      ],
      "answerkey": "0df25198-0cf1-41d7-8f3b-b6c80bb9a6c1",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "questionID": "18bc94e1-2b73-49ae-8be8-e7444265180a",
      "question": "Which is your favourite Song ?",
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "6558b134-02f6-4f58-8865-95a9dbe0c43e",
          "optionValue": "Mausam Mausam"
        },
        {
          "id": "7354bec7-20b3-4418-b797-daf4b534406c",
          "optionValue": "Mere Hath Main"
        },
        {
          "id": "c2358f1c-cf90-49dc-b312-5d0dcba2b74a",
          "optionValue": "Bhool Bhuleya"
        },
        {
          "id": "887bf212-81c0-4579-b094-721b8d8611b6",
          "optionValue": "Meet"
        }
      ],
      "answerkey": "6558b134-02f6-4f58-8865-95a9dbe0c43e",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "questionID": "3310a115-a0f8-46b9-b27b-1b08254c88c7",
      "question": "Which Is Your Favorite Singer?",
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "7987d5ef-3057-4af3-bcf2-7e23a6b9e6cd",
          "optionValue": "Arjit Singh"
        },
        {
          "id": "beeb1829-f16b-4dc1-9bdb-ec6de73096fd",
          "optionValue": "Artif Aslam"
        },
        {
          "id": "c1006fb3-5207-468f-90ac-9cda87dc64a4",
          "optionValue": "Neha Kakkar"
        },
        {
          "id": "8ad1c759-6243-4831-96a9-307bd614027f",
          "optionValue": "Badshah"
        }
      ],
      "answerkey": "beeb1829-f16b-4dc1-9bdb-ec6de73096fd",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "questionID": "b08803c8-f328-405f-ba1a-36990bfbc450",
      "question": "How do you feel when you have no friend?",
      "options": [
        {
          "id": "e3a61b15-7ef1-4a27-ab97-2db0b4f062b4",
          "optionValue": "Good"
        },
        {
          "id": "5eecc469-5ea6-4cea-aebb-bbb2e8684b70",
          "optionValue": "Better"
        },
        {
          "id": "c10fcb12-cb98-4c75-8fe3-83ae546ddab9",
          "optionValue": "Alone"
        },
        {
          "id": "776e25be-94d9-44aa-bba5-840cb00d8659",
          "optionValue": "Sad"
        }
      ],
      "answerkey": "5eecc469-5ea6-4cea-aebb-bbb2e8684b70",
      "id": 10
    }
  ]
}